pleaserusa.com 2017-11-18

# PLEASER USA, THE LEADER IN SEXY & ALTERNATIVE FOOTWEAR

Pleaser USA, Inc. ("Pleaser") respects the privacy of our customers and the users of our website, and has established the following provisions to ensure that your personal information is handled in a responsible manner. Pleaser will not collect, use or disclose your personal information other than in compliance with this Policy. By visiting [www.pleaserusa.com](http://www.pleaserusa.com/), you are accepting the practices described in this policy notice.

Information Collection and Use

Pleaser may collect personal information from you when you provide your personal information to us, such as by setting up a user account and password, logging in as a registered user of [www.pleaserusa.com](http://www.pleaserusa.com/), searching for a product, placing an order, and communicating with us via phone or e-mail, etc. In these instances, we may gather information such as your name, e-mail and postal addresses, phone number(s), credit card information, product interest information, financial information and in certain circumstances, your opinions and personal preferences. Pleaser's website is intended for use by adults. Pleaser does not knowingly retrieve any personal information from children under the age of 13. Those under age 13 should not use Pleaser's website or provide Pleaser with any personal information.

Pleaser uses the personal information collected to confirm and process sales transactions, respond to your customer service inquiries, and contact you with questions or communications about your order. We may also use the information to distribute promotional materials and provide additional information regarding our products, services, surveys, contests, promotions and special offers in order to improve your shopping experience and our product offerings. You will always have the option to not receive promotional materials or marketing information from us.

Third Party Disclosure

Pleaser does not share, sell or rent your personal information to non-affiliated third parties except as permitted by law. However, we may disclose personal information about you to third parties who provide services to us and who agree to maintain the confidentiality of such information in accordance with this privacy policy and use the information only in connection with the services they provide. We may also disclose personal information in circumstances where we have a reason to believe that it is necessary to identify, contact, or bring legal action against someone who may have breached our Terms of Use. 

Security

Pleaser implements a variety of security measures to ensure the confidentiality of personal information and to safeguard against loss or theft, as well as unauthorized access, disclosure, copying, use or modification. All sensitive/credit information you supply is maintained and only accessible by a limited number of persons who have exclusive access rights to such systems, and are required by law to keep the information confidential.

Cookies

Pleaser may use cookies to track your preferences and activities on our website. Cookies are small data files sent to your computer’s hard-drive by a website. They monitor and record your preferences to make your subsequent visits to a site more efficient. This feature enables us to provide you with better services and to also improve your site experience.

You may opt to modify, block, or completely disable cookies (see your browser’s help files for details) and also have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent. However, please note that without cookies, some of the website’s functions will be unavailable, and you may lose some of the benefits of the site.

Changes to Privacy Policy

If changes are made to this Privacy Policy, Pleaser will notify our customers and website users of any such changes by posting an updated policy on our website. Your continued use of the website will constitute your acceptance of these changes and you will be bound by such changes.

Questions about our Policies

We welcome your questions, comments, and concerns about privacy. Please contact us if you have any questions or concerns regarding our privacy or security policies or practices.
